Guide to the Jewish Community Relations Council, Pittsburgh, Pa. Records, 1928-1959 AIS.1965.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publications, 1930-1959; IV.
  - Publications, by Author, L-Z (Box 20)
    - Streit, Clarence K. The Essence of Union Now; New York: The Union Press, 1940; 91.
    - Uhl, Alexander. The Assault on the U.N.; Washington, D.C.: Public Affairs Institute, 1953; 92.
    - United Nations. Secretary-General. The Main Types of Discrimination; Lake Success, New York: United Nations Commission on Human Rights, Sub-Commission on Prevention of Discrimination and Protection of Minorities, 1949; 92a.
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars of the U.S. Fifth Column Facts: A Handbook of Information on Nazi, Fascist and Communist Activities in the United States; Kansas City, Mo., circa 1940; 93.
    - Wallace, Henry A. Century of the Common Man; New York: International Worker Order, 1943; 94.
    - Warburg, James P. The Isolationist Illusion and World Peace; New York: Farrar Rinehart, (America in a World at War #11), 1941; 95.
    - Wilkins, Roy. The Negro Wants Full Equality; New York: The Committee of 100, 1944; 96.
    - Willkie, Wendell L. Americans, Stop Being Afraid!; New York: William E. Rudge's Sons, 1941; 97.
    - Winslow, C. E. A. International Organization for Health; Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, 1944; 98.
    - Wolf, Eleanor P., et al. Negro-Jewish Relations; Detroit: Wayne University, (Wayne University Studies in Inter-groups Conflicts in Detroit #1), 1944; 99.
    - Wisconsin. Governor's Commission on Human Rights. Negro families in rural Wisconsin; Madison, WI, 1949; 100.
    - Workers' Defense League. Labor, Defense, and Democracy; New York, 1939; 101.
    - World Citizens Association. The World at the Crossroads; Chicago, Illinois, 1946; 102.
    - Zocca, Marie Ragonetti. The United Nations: Action for Peace; New Brunswick: Rutgers University Press, 1955; 103.